Guide to the Don Gale KSL editorial video collection 1938-2010 1978-1997
Multimedia Archives, J. Willard Marriott Library, University of Utah
- KSL editorials, 1978-1998; 2010
  - KSL editorials, 1988 January-1988 March; DVD (Disc 55)
    - Control all-terrain vehicles, 1988 March 4 (Video 46)
    - Thanks to the Utah Jazz, 1988 March 7 (Video 47)
    - Reject germ test facility, 1988 March 8 (Video 48)
    - Race for state symbols, 1988 March 9 (Video 49)
    - Emphasize basic values, 1988 March 10 (Video 50)
    - Postal service cuts back, 1988 March 11 (Video 51)
    - Utah State University, 1988 March 14 (Video 52)
    - Another point of view - Joseph S. Rees, re firing coach, 1988 March 15 (Video 53)
    - Questions bring good news, 1988 March 16 (Video 54)
    - Dairy progam goes sour, 1988 March 17 (Video 55)
    - Appeals court proves value, 1988 March 18 (Video 56)
    - Recognizing Utah farmers, 1988 March 21 (Video 57)
    - Another point of view - Thomas Smith, re pest control association, 1988 March 22 (Video 58)
    - AIDS testing fight continues, 1988 March 23 (Video 59)
    - NASA bureaucrats strike Thiokol, 1988 March 24 (Video 60)
    - Support war games arcade, 1988 March 25 (Video 61)
    - Lessons from China, 1988 March 28 (Video 62)
    - Another point of view - William Grigg, re Nicaragua, 1988 March 29 (Video 63)
    - Act now on county jail, 1988 March 30 (Video 64)
    - Line-item veto not the answer, 1988 March 31 (Video 65)
  - KSL editorials, 1988 April-1988 June; DVD (Disc 56)
    - Expanding health insurance, 1988 April 1 (Video 1)
    - No more bugs, 1988 April 4 (Video 2)
    - Another point of view - Peter Ruplinger, re good teachers, 1988 April 5 (Video 3)
    - Tragic waste of resources, 1988 April 6 (Video 4)
    - Marvel of our time, 1988 April 7 (Video 5)
    - Changes in motor fuel, 1988 April 8 (Video 6)
    - Play ball!, 1988 April 11 (Video 7)
    - Another point of view - Don Wilcox, re Sat. postal service, 1988 April 12 (Video 8)
    - Great green garbage cans, 1988 April 13 (Video 9)
    - Mixed news on drug front, 1988 April 14 (Video 10)
    - Working for a better Utah, 1988 April 15 (Video 11)
    - What is freedom worth?, 1988 April 18 (Video 12)
    - Television and the global village, 1988 April 19 (Video 13)
    - Protect the ozone, 1988 April 20 (Video 14)
    - Spring in the air, 1988 April 21 (Video 15)
    - Driver exam needs upgrading, 1988 April 22 (Video 16)
    - National consumer week, 1988 April 25 (Video 17)
    - Jail proposal applauded, 1988 April 26 (Video 18)
    - Facts about taxes, 1988 April 27 (Video 19)
    - Gas line project needs review, 1988 April 28 (Video 20)
    - A day for trees, 1988 April 29 (Video 21)
    - Drug prolem is domestic, 1988 May 2 (Video 22)
    - Changes in the Soviet Union, 1988 May 3 (Video 23)
    - Don't blame postal service, 1988 May 4 (Video 24)
    - Nurse Appreciation Week, 1988 May 5 (Video 25)
    - Paying for school attendance, 1988 May 6 (Video 26)
    - Utah vacation planning time, 1988 May 9 (Video 27)
    - Resist the urge to help, 1988 May 10 (Video 28)
    - Irving Berlin's birthday, 1988 May 11 (Video 29)
    - Tuition savings plan, 1988 May 12 (Video 30)
    - Progress demands nuclear energy, 1988 May 13 (Video 31)
    - Consolidate, consolidate, consolidate, 1988 May 16 (Video 32)
    - Getting out of social security, 1988 May 17 (Video 33)
    - Voting record fading, 1988 May 18 (Video 34)
    - An assault on values, 1988 May 19 (Video 35)
    - Congress exempts itself, 1988 May 20 (Video 36)
    - Preserve and protect hearing, 1988 May 23 (Video 37)
    - Low bid not the answer, 1988 May 24 (Video 38)
    - Join pollution clean-up, 1988 May 25 (Video 39)
    - City-county building restoration, 1988 May 26 (Video 40)
    - Tax retirement benefits, 1988 May 27 (Video 41)
    - Memorial Day, 1988 May 30 (Video 42)
    - Americans should look south, 1988 May 31 (Video 43)
    - Argentina: a nation on hold, 1988 June 1 (Video 44)
    - Lessons from Argentina, 1988 June 2 (Video 45)
    - Chile's textbook economy, 1988 June 3 (Video 46)
    - Learning from Chile, 1988 June 6 (Video 47)
    - Peru and its problems, 1988 June 7 (Video 48)
    - Fighting drugs in Peru, 1988 June 8 (Video 49)
    - Free fishing day, 1988 June 9 (Video 50)
    - A pretty, great state, 1988 June 10 (Video 51)
    - Praise to couny commission, 1988 June 13 (Video 52)
    - Child support guidelines needed, 1988 June 14 (Video 53)
    - Handling the tax rebate, 1988 June 15 (Video 54)
    - South America's foreign debt, 1988 June 16 (Video 55)
    - U.S. vulnerable on oil, 1988 June 17 (Video 56)
    - Let's build new arena, 1988 June 20 (Video 57)
    - Research park construction, 1988 June 21 (Video 58)
    - Resolve failed thrift issue, 1988 June 22 (Video 59)
    - Utah economy turns around, 1988 June 23 (Video 60)
    - Thanks, R/UDAT, 1988 June 24 (Video 61)
    - City police deserve consideration, 1988 June 27 (Video 62)
    - Another point of view - Jerald Merrill, re homeless, 1988 June 28 (Video 63)
    - Thanks to the weekly press, 1988 June 29 (Video 64)
    - Pentagon scandal and drugs, 1988 June 30 (Video 65)
  - KSL editorials, 1988 July-1988 September; DVD (Disc 57)
    - The FBI and books, 1988 July 1 (Video 1)
    - Fourth of July freedom, 1988 July 4 (Video 2)
    - Attend community council meetings, 1988 July 5 (Video 3)
    - Effects of the drought, 1988 July 6 (Video 4)
    - Liquor laws not relevant, 1988 July 7 (Video 5)
    - The power of ideals, 1988 July 8 (Video 6)
    - Ulster project may help, 1988 July 11 (Video 7)
    - Growing shortage of teachers, 1988 July 12 (Video 8)
    - The throwaway society, 1988 July 13 (Video 9)
    - Tragedy on block 57, 1988 July 14 (Video 10)
    - National conventions deserve attention, 1988 July 15 (Video 11)
    - Iranian airliner a symbol, 1988 July 18 (Video 12)
    - Order and democracy, 1988 July 19 (Video 13)
    - Opportunity for education, 1988 July 20 (Video 14)
    - Triad center positive addition, 1988 July 21 (Video 15)
    - Good time to buy home, 1988 July 22 (Video 16)
    - Remember the pioneers, 1988 July 25 (Video 17)
    - Systems versus customers, 1988 July 26 (Video 18)
    - Western water precious, 1988 July 27 (Video 19)
    - Education and dividends, 1988 July 28 (Video 20)
    - Luxury market booming, 1988 July 29 (Video 21)
    - Butterflies are free, 1988 August 1 (Video 22)
    - War on drugs, 1988 August 2 (Video 23)
    - Improve traffic flow, 1988 August 3 (Video 24)
    - Rebuilding the human body (not recorded for archive), 1988 August 4 (Video 25)
    - TV marti compounds mistake, 1988 August 5 (Video 26)
    - Motorcycle helmet laws matter, 1988 August 8 (Video 27)
    - Vaccines and the law, 1988 August 9 (Video 28)
    - Aging baby boomers, 1988 August 10 (Video 29)
    - Salt Palace expansion, 1988 August 11 (Video 30)
    - Vacant lot becomes garden, 1988 August 12 (Video 31)
    - Mountains of trash, 1988 August 15 (Video 32)
    - Another point of view - Greg Beesley, re government waste, 1988 August 16 (Video 33)
    - Economic picture brightens, 1988 August 17 (Video 34)
    - Stress prenatal care, 1988 August 18 (Video 35)
    - Representative government, 1988 August 19 (Video 36)
    - Preparing for school, 1988 August 22 (Video 37)
    - Get together on CUP, 1988 August 23 (Video 38)
    - Value of one teacher, 1988 August 24 (Video 39)
    - Fair stays where it is, 1988 August 25 (Video 40)
    - Buy from Utah business, 1988 August 26 (Video 41)
    - Offensive bumper stickers, 1988 August 29 (Video 42)
    - Another point of view - Bob Wilkins, re business systems, 1988 August 30 (Video 43)
    - Research benefits ulcer victims, 1988 August 31 (Video 44)
    - Sporting events ban beer, 1988 September 1 (Video 45)
    - Housing costs too high, 1988 September 2 (Video 46)
    - Revival of patriotism, 1988 September 5 (Video 47)
    - Revising Utah's economy, 1988 September 6 (Video 48)
    - Don't restrict information services, 1988 September 7 (Video 49)
    - Lake has last laugh, 1988 September 8 (Video 50)
    - Push ahead on land trade, 1988 September 9 (Video 51)
    - Utah's high taxes, 1988 September 12 (Video 52)
    - Utah State Fair week, 1988 September 13 (Video 53)
    - Settle musician strike, 1988 September 14 (Video 54)
    - Balancing taxes and services, 1988 September 15 (Video 55)
    - Fighting forest fires, 1988 September 16 (Video 56)
    - Science and the olympics (not recorded for archive), 1988 September 19 (Video 57)
    - Constitution month, 1988 September 20 (Video 58)
    - Consider today's realities, 1988 September 21 (Video 59)
    - False savings at university, 1988 September 22 (Video 60)
    - Government employment in Utah, 1988 September 23 (Video 61)
    - Visit Boulder Mountain, 1988 September 26 (Video 62)
    - Campaigns don't change, 1988 September 27 (Video 63)
    - The tax initiatives, 1988 September 28 (Video 64)
    - Millionaire lawmakers, 1988 September 29 (Video 65)
    - Living in the canyons, 1988 September 30 (Video 66)
  - KSL editorials, 1988 October-1988 December; DVD (Disc 58)
    - Morris is dead, 1988 October 3 (Video 1)
    - Symphony needs your support, 1988 October 4 (Video 2)
    - Tax rollback initiative, 1988 October 5 (Video 3)
    - Protect latchkey children, 1988 October 6 (Video 4)
    - The silly season, 1988 October 7 (Video 5)
    - American is back in apace, 1988 October 10 (Video 6)
    - Utah poised for growth, 1988 October 11 (Video 7)
    - Private education initiative, 1988 October 12 (Video 8)
    - Greenhouse effect again, 1988 October 13 (Video 9)
    - Utah and other states, 1988 October 14 (Video 10)
    - Watch for learning disabilities, 1988 October 17 (Video 11)
    - Turmoil in Chile, 1988 October 18 (Video 12)
    - Property tax initiative, 1988 October 19 (Video 13)
    - Raising the minimum wage, 1988 October 20 (Video 14)
    - Dealing with problems, 1988 October 21 (Video 15)
    - United Nations week, 1988 October 24 (Video 16)
    - Another point of view - Reid Swenson, re tax rollback, 1988 October 25 (Video 17)
    - Red ribbon week, 1988 October 26 (Video 18)
    - Tax rollback not wise, 1988 October 27 (Video 19)
    - Six months of sunshine, 1988 October 28 (Video 20)
    - Boil the ocean, 1988 October 31 (Video 21)
    - Another point of view - Senator Bill Barton, re cost of education, 1988 November 1 (Video 22)
    - Another point of view - David Fiske, re cost effective government, 1988 November 2 (Video 23)
    - Another point of view - Glenn Davis, re tax limitation initiative, 1988 November 3 (Video 24)
    - Voting on tax initiatives, 1988 November 4 (Video 25)
    - Vote, vote, vote!, 1988 November 7 (Video 26)
    - Center of the world market, 1988 November 8 (Video 27)
    - Thanks to Union Pacific, 1988 November 9 (Video 28)
    - Editorials often unpopular, 1988 November 10 (Video 29)
    - Expanding soviet exchanges, 1988 November 11 (Video 30)
    - The beauty of democracy, 1988 November 14 (Video 31)
    - Dealing with hazardous waste, 1988 November 15 (Video 32)
    - Working without tools, 1988 November 16 (Video 33)
    - Thanks, American Express, 1988 November 17 (Video 34)
    - Read catalogs; buy Utah, 1988 November 18 (Video 35)
    - Tuition increases make sense, 1988 November 21 (Video 36)
    - Remembering a dark day, 1988 November 22 (Video 37)
    - Thanksgiving, 1988 November 23 (Video 38)
    - Thank historical leaders, 1988 November 24 (Video 39)
    - Geographic illiterates, 1988 November 25 (Video 40)
    - Taking good advice, 1988 November 28 (Video 41)
    - Deficit first priority, 1988 November 29 (Video 42)
    - Your worst enemy, 1988 November 30 (Video 43)
    - Teenage smoking not rebellion, 1988 December 1 (Video 44)
    - Computers have virus, too, 1988 December 2 (Video 45)
    - Paramedic service privatized?, 1988 December 5 (Video 46)
    - Full circle corner, 1988 December 6 (Video 47)
    - Utah libraries in trouble, 1988 December 7 (Video 48)
    - Warnings on alcohol, 1988 December 8 (Video 49)
    - Learning to live with chemicals, 1988 December 9 (Video 50)
    - Quarters for Christmas, 1988 December 12 (Video 51)
    - Give, but do it wisely, 1988 December 13 (Video 52)
    - Wipe out discrimination, 1988 December 14 (Video 53)
    - The christmas flower, 1988 December 15 (Video 54)
    - Scientific illiteracy, 1988 December 16 (Video 55)
    - Stealth bomber unneeded, 1988 December 19 (Video 56)
    - Behind the scenes help, 1988 December 20 (Video 57)
    - Wouldn't it be nice..., 1988 December 21 (Video 58)
    - Global village grows smaller, 1988 December 22 (Video 59)
    - Christmas beginnings, 1988 December 23 (Video 60)
    - Drinking and driving, 1988 December 26 (Video 61)
    - Gorbachev's United Nations speech, 1988 December 27 (Video 62)
    - PLO decision wise, 1988 December 28 (Video 63)
    - Nuclear weapons halted, 1988 December 29 (Video 64)
    - Welcome the new year, 1988 December 30 (Video 65)
  - KSL editorials, 1989 January-1989 March; DVD (Disc 59)
    - Housing and equity sharing, 1989 January 2 (Video 1)
    - "Bare bones" budget, 1989 January 3 (Video 2)
    - Pay raise for congress, 1989 January 4 (Video 3)
    - Living with risk, 1989 January 5 (Video 4)
    - Quality education in Utah, 1989 January 6 (Video 5)
    - Dealing with terrorism, 1989 January 9 (Video 6)
    - Closing Fort Douglas, 1989 January 10 (Video 7)
    - Remaking the court, 1989 January 11 (Video 8)
    - Dealing with gridlock, 1989 January 12 (Video 9)
    - School critics need update, 1989 January 13 (Video 10)
    - Challenges for the legislature, 1989 January 16 (Video 11)
    - Thanks to snow crews, 1989 January 17 (Video 12)
    - Savings and loan problems, 1989 January 18 (Video 13)
    - The Reagan years, 1989 January 19 (Video 14)
    - Challenges for President Bush, 1989 January 20 (Video 15)
    - Thanks to legislators, 1989 January 23 (Video 16)
    - Anticipating the seasons, 1989 January 24 (Video 17)
    - Diking Great Salt Lake, 1989 January 25 (Video 18)
    - Return to the old west, 1989 January 26 (Video 19)
    - Pay raises for Congress, 1989 January 27 (Video 20)
    - Utah judges deserve more, 1989 January 30 (Video 21)
    - Primary Children's Medical Center, 1989 January 31 (Video 22)
    - Education gets 'tough', 1989 February 1 (Video 23)
    - Year of the young reader, 1989 February 2 (Video 24)
    - Chemical weapons ban, 1989 February 3 (Video 25)
    - Sales tax on food, 1989 February 6 (Video 26)
    - Another point of view - Elliot C. Howe, re study of foreign languages, 1989 February 7 (Video 27)
    - Community college month, 1989 February 8 (Video 28)
    - Retain state school board, 1989 February 9 (Video 29)
    - Control computer phoning, 1989 February 10 (Video 30)
    - Building a better image, 1989 February 13 (Video 31)
    - Helping the community, 1989 February 14 (Video 32)
    - Learning about the USSR, 1989 February 15 (Video 33)
    - Of roads and autos, 1989 February 16 (Video 34)
    - Control leveraged buyouts, 1989 February 17 (Video 35)
    - Freedoms Awareness Week, 1989 February 20 (Video 36)
    - Another point of view - David Hemingway, re dike Great Salt Lake, 1989 February 21 (Video 37)
    - George Washington, 1989 February 22 (Video 38)
    - Black History Month, 1989 February 23 (Video 39)
    - Honoring boy scouts, 1989 February 24 (Video 40)
    - Closed meeting dangers, 1989 February 27 (Video 41)
    - Another point of view - Jake D. Huff, re state education standards, 1989 February 28 (Video 42)
    - Legislative log jam, 1989 March 1 (Video 43)
    - Savings and loan problem, 1989 March 2 (Video 44)
    - Voter turnout problems, 1989 March 3 (Video 45)
    - National Volunteer Week, 1989 March 6 (Video 46)
    - Another point of view - Paul Neuenschwander, re savings/loans, 1989 March 7 (Video 47)
    - Power of words, 1989 March 8 (Video 48)
    - Fort Douglas will remain, 1989 March 9 (Video 49)
    - Legislature let us down, 1989 March 10 (Video 50)
    - Improve 911 service, 1989 March 13 (Video 51)
    - Pay raise for Congress, 1989 March 14 (Video 52)
    - Stop gangs now, 1989 March 15 (Video 53)
    - Freedom of information, 1989 March 16 (Video 54)
    - Hold firm on rule 42, 1989 March 17 (Video 55)
    - Make arena large enough, 1989 March 20 (Video 56)
    - Pollution and trees, 1989 March 21 (Video 57)
    - Skirmish on drugs, 1989 March 22 (Video 58)
    - Tax laws workable, 1989 March 23 (Video 59)
    - Washington's changing standards, 1989 March 24 (Video 60)
    - Utah's changing economy, 1989 March 27 (Video 61)
    - Does Utah want tourists?, 1989 March 28 (Video 62)
    - Think about seat belts, 1989 March 29 (Video 63)
    - Year 'round schools, 1989 March 30 (Video 64)
    - Sleight of hand deficits, 1989 March 31 (Video 65)
  - KSL editorials, 1989 April-1989 June; DVD (Disc 60)
    - Review city golf program, 1989 April 3 (Video 1)
    - Another point of view - Joe Duke-Rosati, re tax education and services, 1989 April 4 (Video 2)
    - Dayling saving time, 1989 April 5 (Video 3)
    - The fuss over fusion, 1989 April 6 (Video 4)
    - Apple scare irrational, 1989 April 7 (Video 5)
    - National Library Week, 1989 April 10 (Video 6)
    - Fund fusion research, 1989 April 11 (Video 7)
    - Thinking about gun control, 1989 April 12 (Video 8)
    - Education by the numbers, 1989 April 13 (Video 9)
    - The cost of defense, 1989 April 14 (Video 10)
    - Wise choice on arena, 1989 April 17 (Video 11)
    - An American tragedy, 1989 April 18 (Video 12)
    - See Utah first, 1989 April 19 (Video 13)
    - Protect CUP concept, 1989 April 20 (Video 14)
    - Ethics and everyday behavior, 1989 April 21 (Video 15)
    - Organ donor awareness week, 1989 April 24 (Video 16)
    - Fans are not participants, 1989 April 25 (Video 17)
    - School superintendent under fire, 1989 April 26 (Video 18)
    - Celebrate the city, 1989 April 27 (Video 19)
    - Arbor Day, 1989 April 28 (Video 20)
    - Utah Jazz are winners, 1989 May 1 (Video 21)
    - Rising gasoline prices, 1989 May 2 (Video 22)
    - New jail facility needed, 1989 May 3 (Video 23)
    - Agency needs supervision, 1989 May 4 (Video 24)
    - Consolidate economic development, 1989 May 5 (Video 25)
    - Challenge of the olympics, 1989 May 8 (Video 26)
    - Seeking compromise on the environment, 1989 May 9 (Video 27)
    - Excellence in education, 1989 May 10 (Video 28)
    - Oliver North's journey, 1989 May 11 (Video 29)
    - Get rid of rats, 1989 May 12 (Video 30)
    - Tourism week in Utah, 1989 May 15 (Video 31)
    - Geneva Steel under attack, 1989 May 16 (Video 32)
    - Families in need of help, 1989 May 17 (Video 33)
    - School "choice" no answer, 1989 May 18 (Video 34)
    - Stop skinhead movement, 1989 May 19 (Video 35)
    - Stick with cold fusion, 1989 May 22 (Video 36)
    - Another point of view - Paul Wayman, re hazardous waste fees, 1989 May 23 (Video 37)
    - Safetey and highway lighting, 1989 May 24 (Video 38)
    - Radio goes silent, 1989 May 25 (Video 39)
    - World grows safer, 1989 May 26 (Video 40)
    - A pretty, great state, 1989 May 29 (Video 41)
    - Another point of view - Jack Greene, re wilderness legislation, 1989 May 30 (Video 42)
    - Utah's school report card, 1989 May 31 (Video 43)
    - Forty years of television, 1989 June 1 (Video 44)
    - Great time to be alive, 1989 June 2 (Video 45)
    - Nation's business needs attention, 1989 June 5 (Video 46)
    - Another point of view - Glen Davis, re school choice, 1989 June 6 (Video 47)
    - Review education funding, 1989 June 7 (Video 48)
    - Delay custodial care, 1989 June 8 (Video 49)
    - America's bridge is falling down, 1989 June 9 (Video 50)
    - Marking 25 years of service, 1989 June 12 (Video 51)
    - Value of olympic choice, 1989 June 13 (Video 52)
    - Flag Day, 1989 June 14 (Video 53)
    - Unrest in China, 1989 June 15 (Video 54)
    - Hotel Utah continues, 1989 June 16 (Video 55)
    - President's clean air program, 1989 June 19 (Video 56)
    - Hiring the handicapped, 1989 June 20 (Video 57)
    - The challenge of consistency, 1989 June 21 (Video 58)
    - More medical marvels due, 1989 June 22 (Video 59)
    - Libel laws need reform, 1989 June 23 (Video 60)
    - Drug war heating up, 1989 June 26 (Video 61)
    - Lyme disease scare overstated, 1989 June 27 (Video 62)
    - It won't work, 1989 June 28 (Video 63)
    - Hazardous waste at home, 1989 June 29 (Video 64)
    - Rural hospitals struggle, 1989 June 30 (Video 65)
  - KSL editorials, 1989 July-1989 September; DVD (Disc 61)
    - How to handle stress, 1989 July 3 (Video 1)
    - Fourth of July, 1989 July 4 (Video 2)
    - Don't consolidate school districts, 1989 July 5 (Video 3)
    - Wonders of time travel, 1989 July 6 (Video 4)
    - Beware of marketing gimmicks, 1989 July 7 (Video 5)
    - Russian olympic lessons, 1989 July 10 (Video 6)
    - Another point of view - Mary Slover, re air pollution from Geneva, 1989 July 11 (Video 7)
    - Fly the flag, 1989 July 12 (Video 8)
    - Federal spending in Utah, 1989 July 13 (Video 9)
    - Sixty years for the choir, 1989 July 14 (Video 10)
    - Thanks to General Koop, 1989 July 17 (Video 11)
    - Business and education, 1989 July 18 (Video 12)
    - Prison camps no answer, 1989 July 19 (Video 13)
    - Men on the moon, 1989 July 20 (Video 14)
    - Need for cooperation, 1989 July 21 (Video 15)
    - Remember the future, 1989 July 24 (Video 16)
    - Review election laws, 1989 July 25 (Video 17)
    - Economic future of Utah, 1989 July 26 (Video 18)
    - Reduce infant mortality, 1989 July 27 (Video 19)
    - Housing problem grows worse, 1989 July 28 (Video 20)
    - Side effects of crime, 1989 July 31 (Video 21)
    - Competing with the Japanese, 1989 August 1 (Video 22)
    - Miracles of medical science, 1989 August 2 (Video 23)
    - Cynicism's growing danger, 1989 August 3 (Video 24)
    - Happy birthday, President Benson, 1989 August 4 (Video 25)
    - Jackson School award, 1989 August 7 (Video 26)
    - Mideast cauldron boils, 1989 August 8 (Video 27)
    - Faculty salaries need boost, 1989 August 9 (Video 28)
    - Long, hot summer, 1989 August 10 (Video 29)
    - Saving solves problems, 1989 August 11 (Video 30)
    - Freedom of speech, 1989 August 14 (Video 31)
    - Another point of view - Howard Stephenson, re school districts, 1989 August 15 (Video 32)
    - William F. Edwards, 1989 August 16 (Video 33)
    - Canada tries a new coin, 1989 August 17 (Video 34)
    - Philo Farnsworth, 1989 August 18 (Video 35)
    - Governor's conference on family, 1989 August 21 (Video 36)
    - President supports pay raise, 1989 August 22 (Video 37)
    - Deteriorating public facilities, 1989 August 23 (Video 38)
    - Ready for energy shortage, 1989 August 24 (Video 39)
    - First amendment worldwide, 1989 August 25 (Video 40)
    - Tax surplus and rollbacks, 1989 August 28 (Video 41)
    - Rethink B-2 bomber, 1989 August 29 (Video 42)
    - Back to school, 1989 August 30 (Video 43)
    - Don't expect fewer cars, 1989 August 31 (Video 44)
    - Income and prosperity (not recorded for archive), 1989 September 1 (Video 45)
    - Changes in east Europe (not recorded for archive), 1989 September 4 (Video 46)
    - Utah State Fair (not recorded for archive), 1989 September 5 (Video 47)
    - Working with reality (not recorded for archive), 1989 September 6 (Video 48)
    - State lottery sham (not recorded for archive), 1989 September 7 (Video 49)
    - Dealing with risk (not recorded for archive), 1989 September 8 (Video 50)
    - War on drugs - still (not recorded for archive), 1989 September 11 (Video 51)
    - The lost generation (not recorded for archive), 1989 September 12 (Video 52)